http://www.webdancers.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footerHomeServicesWeb DesignWordPress WebsitesHosting and SupportWebsite EncryptionPortfolioTestimonialsAboutBlogOnline ToolsOnline MarketingCommunityLocal BusinessSocial MediaContactWebdancersWe build engaging websites that help your customers find you.Privacy PolicyThings you should know:Webdancers ("Webdancers")
operates www.webdancers.com and may operate other websites. It
is Webdancers' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect
while operating our websites.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Webdancers collects non-personally-identifying information of the
sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference,
referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Webdancers' purpose in
collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand
how Webdancers' visitors use its website. From time to
time, Webdancers may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by
publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Webdancers also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol
(IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on www.webdancers.com
blogs/sites. Webdancers only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same
circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that
commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site
where the comment was left.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Webdancers' websites choose to interact
with Webdancers in ways that require Webdancers to gather
personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Webdancers gathers
depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at www.webdancers.com to provide a
username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Webdancers are asked to
provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to
process those transactions. In each case, Webdancers collects such information only insofar as
is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with
Webdancers. Webdancers does not disclose personally-identifying information
other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with
the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Aggregated StatisticsWebdancers may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its
websites. Webdancers may display this information publicly or provide it to others.
However, Webdancers does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as
described below.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationWebdancers discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information
only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information
in order to process it on Webdancers' behalf or to provide services available
at Webdancers' websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some
of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by
using Webdancers' websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to
them. Webdancers will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated
organizations, as described above, Webdancers discloses potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or
when Webdancers believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the
property or rights of Webdancers, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered
user of an Webdancers website and have supplied your email address, Webdancers
may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to
date with what's going on with Webdancers and our products. If you send us a request (for
example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us
clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Webdancers takes all
measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of
potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser
provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Webdancers uses cookies to
help Webdancers identify and track visitors, their usage of Webdancers
website, and their website access preferences. Webdancers visitors who do not wish to have
cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before
using Webdancers' websites, with the drawback that certain features
of Webdancers' websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Business TransfersIf Webdancers, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event
that Webdancers goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the
assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that
any acquirer of Webdancers may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this
policy.AdsAds appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.
These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to
compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among
other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy
Policy covers the use of cookies by Webdancers and does not cover the use of cookies by any
advertisers.Things you should know ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Webdancers may change
its Things you should know from time to time, and in Webdancers' sole
discretion. Webdancers encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to
its Things you should know. If you have a www.webdancers.com account, you might also
receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in
this Things you should know will constitute your acceptance of such change.Primary SidebarWe build elegant and effective websites for local businesses that connect with customers. Contact us for a free consultation.Contact UsWe had a very antiquated website and Webdancers came highly recommended. They developed a new interactive website which we can maintain and manage. Webdancers understands what a client’s needs are, and their staff is very friendly and professional. If you have things that need to be adjusted, even after the project’s completion, they are more than willing to take care of it in a timely manner.Sandra AsquithTwain Harte Area Chamber of CommerceLike what you see here? Get More.Our weekly newsletter brings you news you can use from the world of tech, online communications and our own home town.
Email
First Name
Please wait...
Thank you for signing up!
Newsletter archiveFooterFacebookLinkedInTwitterContact Us
Webdancers
320 W. Stockton St.
Sonora,
Who needs the internet?
September 20, 2019
What will you commit to?
July 26, 2019@webdancers
Copyright © 1995–2020 Webdancers ·
Built on WordPress and the
Genesis Framework · Privacy policyHome page photo by Naotake Murayama · Log in
